

CONTACT

+48 509 646 459
OLGA.KACALA@GMAIL.COM
OPOLE, POLAND
FIND ME ON LINKEDIN
CHECK MY GITHUB PROFILE

PROFILE

Since beginning of my professional journey I have learned and work close to the production process needs and challenges. Thru years I have worked with Production Team in order to optimize available process control tools. Now I want to be a part of Development Team and be able to use my understanding of user experience needs.

SKILLS

New at:

- HTML, CSS
- Java Script
- React
- TypeScript
- Jest, Cypress

Strong:

- optimising MES user experience with IT developers
- ISO 9001; 14001; 45001, CE
- Scrum, Jira, Git
- English: C1

EDUCATION

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

INFOSHARE ACADEMY SP. Z O.O. | NOV 2022 - FEB 2023 (445H TOTAL WHERE 240H WITH EXPERTS)

- Working in: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Git, Webpack, Firebase
- Responsive website and application layout
- HTTP and network communication
- Static code analysis (Jest) and e2e tests (Cypress)
- Single Page Apps (SPA)
- Scrum (Jira) and teamwork

Check out my final project: PANDOTEKA

MASTER'S DEGREE 20012 - 2013

ENGINEER'S DEGREE 2008 -2012

UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY IN KRAKÓW

Faculty of Material Science and Ceramics

Field of Study - Chemical Technology

Field of Specialization - Technology of Building Materials

EXPERIENCE

QHSE MANAGER

MCBRIDE; STRZELCE OPOLSKIE | DEC 2020 - NOV 2022

- Managing H&S, Environmental and Quality Department with 2 laboratories
- Developing and coordinating root cause analyses with multi department team
- Maintaining the H&S and Environmental standards within ISO 14001 and 45001.

BUSINESS UNIT QHSE MANAGER

SKAMOL; OPOLE | FEB 2019 - DEC 2020

- Standardization of QHSE procedures in BU Boards production plants (Denmark & Poland) by uniform MES system
- Management of Zero Defect & Zero Water Project in the Group
- Leading implementation project of new production line in Opole plant

PROCESS & QUALITY MANAGER

SKAMOL; OPOLE | OCT 2018 - FEB 2019

- Extension of Quality Department
- Verification of product quality against cost of production
- Handling of the Customer Claims
- Performing internal audits (DK/PL plants)

PROCESS & QUALITY SPECIALIST

SKAMOL; OPOLE | FEB 2017 - OCT 2018

- Creating a new quality laboratory and setting procedures
- Member of the Start-up Team in Opole plant
- Preparation to ISO 9001 and CE marking audits

ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGIST

THE INSTITUTE OF CERAMICS AND BUILDING MATERIALS;
OPOLE | JUN 2014 - FEB 2017

INTERNSHIP

GÓRAŻDŻE CEMENT S.A. HEIDELBERGCEMENT GROUP | MAR - MAJ 2013